zensar.com 2019-05-13

# Privacy Policy | Zensar

**Zensar Privacy Policy**  

This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 25, 2018.  

 **Preamble**

Zensar Technologies Ltd., and its affiliated entities around the world (collectively “Zensar”, “we”, or “us”), is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout our company governing Zensar’s use of personal information about:

  * visitors to our Internet website (the “Site”) located at the URL: www.Zensar.com, and
  * employees of our clients who use our services and/or products (collectively, services and products are: “Service” or “Services”).

Where the Privacy Policy differs depending on whether you are using the Site or the Services, those distinctions will be noted in this Privacy Policy.  

 **Information Collection**  

 **Through the Site:**  

You can generally visit the Site without revealing any personal information about yourself. "Personal information" is any information that can be used to identify an individual, and may include name, address, email address, phone number, login information (account number, password), marketing preferences, or social media account information. However, in certain sections of the Site we may invite you to contact us for information or questions, inquire about a job or apply for a job, or to obtain content we provide for informational and marketing purposes.  In such situations, you may disclose to us your name, phone number, email address, title, company name, and certain employment-related information.

We may track and store information such as the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, your IP address, your browser type, the number of external web site (defined below) pages you have visited, and other browsing or computer data.

 **Through the Services:**  

When our clients use our Services, our clients may provide us with information about you, including personal information such as your name, address, email, phone number and IP address

 **Use of Information**  

We may use your personal information you submit to the Site to:

  * contact you to deliver certain information you have requested
  * verify your authority to enter our Site
  * consider your eligibility for employment
  * improve the content and general administration of the Site
  * address any queries or provide necessary information/resources
  * contact you in relation to your registration for an event/webinar
  * contact the users who have provided their information with respect to any service line

Zensar uses the information Zensar receives through our clients’ use of the Services to provide our Services to our clients under their direction and instruction.  

 **Disclosure and Onward Transfer of Information**  

We will not rent or sell your personal information to any company or organization. We may provide your personal information to our subsidiaries and affiliates. We may provide your personal information to vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us in providing our Services to our clients, or to assist us in verifying your eligibility for employment with Zensar. Such third parties will be restricted from further distributing your personal information and must enter into a written confidentiality agreement with us. We will also disclose your personal information if we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority, or otherwise in cooperation with a bona-fide investigation of a governmental or other public authority, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, or to protect the safety of visitors to our Site. We may transfer your personal information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Zensar participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Zensar’s assets to which the Site and/or Services relate.

 **Links to Third Party Sites**  

The Site may provide links to other web sites or resources over which Zensar does not have control (“External Web Sites”). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Zensar of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that Zensar is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that Zensar is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the External Web Sites.

 **Limiting the Use of Personal Information Collected Through the Site and Services**  

You can limit our use of personal information collected through our Site by following the instructions at the bottom of each email we send you. You can limit our use of personal information that we obtain via our Services by managing your account at the respective client with whom you interact.

 **Reviewing, Correcting and Deleting Personal Information Collected Through the Site**  

Zensar provides you with the ability to review, correct, and delete your personal information that we have received if it is inaccurate or you wish us to delete it; provided, however, that Zensar will retain a copy in its files of all personal information, even if corrected, necessary to resolve disputes. Zensar retains personal information you submit through our Site for up to 4 years in connection with regulatory, tax, insurance or other requirements in the places in which it operates. Zensar thereafter deletes or anonymizes such information in accordance with applicable laws. You have the right to review or delete the foregoing information, by contacting Zensar at:

 **General Counsel**  

Zensar Technologies Ltd.

Zensar Knowledge Park

Kharadi, Plot #4, MIDC, Off Nagar Road

Pune 411 014, India 

 **Special Information for EU Users**  

Beginning May 25, 2018, the processing of personal data of users in the European Union is subject to the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). This section provides information as relates to EU users' rights, and Zensar's responsibilities, under this regulation.

 **1\. EU User Rights**  

If you are a Zensar user in the EU, you have the following rights with respect to Zensar's handling of your personal information. To exercise these rights, please see below.

Users outside the EU may also request explanation, correction, deletion or copies of their personal data, as described above in this Privacy Policy.

 **Explanation and copies of your data**  

  * You have the right to request an explanation of the information that Zensar has about you and how Zensar uses that information.
  * You also have the right to receive a copy of the information that Zensar collects about you if collected on the basis of consent or because Zensar requires the information to provide the services that you request.  

 **Correction**  

  * If Zensar has information about you that you believe is inaccurate, you have the right to request correction of your information. Please see the section titled “Reviewing, Correcting and Deleting Personal Information Collected Through the Site” above for more information on correcting, or requesting correction of, your information.  

 **Deletion**  

  * You may request deletion of your personal information at any time. We may retain certain information about you as required by law and for legitimate business purposes permitted by law.  Please see the “Reviewing, Correcting and Deleting Personal Information Collected Through the Site” section above for more information regarding Zensar's retention and deletion practices.  

 **Objections and complaints**  

  * Users in the EU have the right to object to Zensar's processing of personal information, including for marketing purposes based on profiling and/or automated decision making. Zensar may continue to process your information notwithstanding the objection to the extent permitted under GDPR.
  * Users in the EU also have the right to file a complaint relating to Zensar's handling of your personal information with the UK Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK Data Protection Authority. Their contact information is as follows:  

 **Information Commissioner’s Office**  

Wycliffe House

Water Lane

Wilmslow

Cheshire

SK9 5AF

Tel: 0303 123 1113

You may also submit questions, comments or complaints to Zensar's Data Protection Officer, at [dpo@zensar.com](mailto:dpo@zensar.com).

 **2\. Grounds for Processing**

The GDPR requires that companies processing the personal information of EU users do so on the basis of specific legal grounds. As described below, Zensar processes the information of EU users based on one or more of the grounds specified under the GDPR:

  * The processing is necessary for Zensar's legitimate interests
  * Zensar collects and uses personal information to the extent necessary for its legitimate interests. This includes collecting and using information:
  * To understand how people use our products and services.
  * To perform background checks necessary to verify employment eligibility.
  * To provide customer support.
  * To optimize our service and develop new services. 
  * For research and analytical purposes. 
  * For direct marketing purposes. This includes, for example, analysing data to identify trends and tailor marketing messages to user needs.
  * The processing is necessary to fulfill Zensar's legal obligations
  * Zensar may process your personal information when we have a legal obligation to do so, for example, if we’re responding to a legal process or an enforceable governmental request. 
  * Consent
  * Zensar may collect and use your personal information on the basis of your consent. You may revoke your consent at any time. If you revoke your consent, you will not be able to use any service or feature that requires collection or use of the information we collected or used on the basis of consent.  

 **Security**  

We employ procedural and technological measures that are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Zensar uses Transport Layer Security, firewalls, password protection and takes other physical and logical security measures and places internal restrictions on who within Zensar may access your data to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information. Our security is annually audited by a third party, under the ISO27001:2013 standard and additionally to comply with the PCI-DSS version 3.2 for specific client Services.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping that password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. You also acknowledge that your account is personal to you and agree not to provide any other person with access to this Site or portions of it using your user name, password or other security information. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized access to or use of your user name or password or any other breach of security. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, as described above, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Site. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site.

 **Children’s Privacy**  

Zensar recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. The Site is not intended for children under the age of 13. Zensar does not target the Site to children under 13. Zensar does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

If we learn that we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification or parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any such information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us at:

 **General Counsel**  

Zensar Technologies Ltd.

Zensar Knowledge Park

Kharadi, Plot #4, MIDC, Off Nagar Road

Pune 411 014, India 

 **Cookies**  

In order to enhance your experience on our sites, our web pages use "cookies". Cookies are small text files that we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personal information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our Site. Once you choose to provide a web page with personal information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. A cookie is like a unique identity card. It is unique to your computer and can only be read by the server that gave it to you.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our Site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience on our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our Site). We also may use cookies to offer you services.

Cookies save you time as they help us to remember who you are. Cookies help us to be more efficient. We can learn about what content is important to you and what is not. If you are concerned about cookies, you can turn them off in your browser.

The full details of all the cookies set by www.zensar.com are below:

Marketo - Marketo tracking cookies allow us to collect information about how you use our Site after you have received an email from us. The cookies track data linked to your email address and include data such as how you arrived at the Site, how often you've visited, and which pages you looked at.

Google Analytics - The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, but include data such as how you arrived at the Site, how often you've visited, and which pages you looked at. We use the information to compile reports using Google Analytics. To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all Zensar websites, visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

The following links explain how to block cookies in your browser:

 **Privacy Policy Updates**  

Due to the Internet’s rapidly evolving nature, Zensar may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, Zensar will post a notice of the change and the updated Privacy Policy on our Site located at <https://www.zensar.com/privacy-policy>. We may also send registered visitors of the Site e-mail notifications notifying such visitors of any changes to the Privacy Policy. If any change is unacceptable to you, you have the right to cease using this Site. If you do not cease using this Site, you will be deemed to have accepted Zensar’s then current Privacy Policy.  

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us via e-mail at: [dpo@zensar.com](mailto:dpo@zensar.com).
